<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mahaboobtech</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/</link><description>Recent content on mahaboobtech</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:25:19 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mahaboobtech.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GET YOUR OWN WEBSITE</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/shop/get_website/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 17:57:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/shop/get_website/</guid><description>GET YOUR OWN WEBSITE – AFFORDABLE, PROFESSIONAL &amp;amp; SEO-READY
We Help You Build Your Online Presence #Want to launch your personal blog, portfolio, or business online? We offer affordable website creation services with the quality and performance you need.
Note:
Domain charges are separate and must be handled by the customer. For Dynamic Websites, server charges will be applied to the customer, depending on the website&amp;rsquo;s complexity and expected traffic. These charges vary based on the resources and hosting requirements.</description></item><item><title>Hyderabad Foods</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/offtopic/hyderabad-foods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 07:18:08 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/offtopic/hyderabad-foods/</guid><description>hello bhojana priyulara 😂, i am making the blog for food lovers who are at hyderabad, in this blog i will mention few places and few dishes which are famous in Hyderabad which you need definately try it atleast once in your life.
note this blog may update time to time, if you know few famous places &amp;amp; dishes you can email us about that particular place email : mickelbasha1268@gmail.com</description></item><item><title>Quotes Logic</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/offtopic/quotes-logic/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 16:28:21 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/offtopic/quotes-logic/</guid><description>life #welcome here guys, this one is special blog because it is wrote with a lot of experience and feelings. here i am going to give few quotes which i think it may impact in your life and may help to superfiy your way of living and realize the motive of the life and to know how beautifull is life, to know how painfull is life , to know how this life journey is &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Relationship</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/offtopic/relationship/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:54:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/offtopic/relationship/</guid><description>If you want to maintain a good, healthy relationship, then this article is for you, especially for introverts who are hesitant to talk.
Feeling of Introverts #Introverts in relationships often face difficulties maintaining connections. Especially in boyfriend-girlfriend relationships, they tend to stay silent and not talk much. However, they wish they could be like Remo in the movie Aparichith. Introverts often rely on facial expressions; they don&amp;rsquo;t talk much but instead observe others and stay silent, which leads to their behavior going unrecognized.</description></item><item><title>Wifi_vulnerablities</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/tech/wifi_vulnerablities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:50:55 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/tech/wifi_vulnerablities/</guid><description>see folks hacking WIFI is not a simple thing and if you use it for bad thing then it is crime and offense but this article about how to secure your network and what are the vulnerabilities lets get start
first we need to know about the security protocols of the wifi wep released on 1997 which is algorithm is easily breakable wpa released on 2003 which was temporary solution for wep wpa2 released on 2004 which is the most expandable usage protocol and it is vulnerable wpa3 released on 2018 which is most secure but still it can be hackable method called dragonblood</description></item><item><title>Phone_number</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/prog/phone_number/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:55:54 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/prog/phone_number/</guid><description>while i was chatting with my friends on WhatsApp and telegram, where i have all the numbers of my B.Tech friends but problem is they don&amp;rsquo;t have my number because i was introvert so they dont know me well even though i have pretty friends to chat well thats not the point here, i was wondering what if i have the all the Indian number in my whatsapp so that i can see their status and also telegram status and signal status well that is the point where i got this content and it is a disaster for me , let me explain what are the problems I have got</description></item><item><title>Fileshare</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/tech/fileshare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 16:13:17 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/tech/fileshare/</guid><description>Intro #windows file sharing is very important this days especially when you are working in IT company, you need to ask files from your colleague desktop or you need to draw some file from another computer or you may need to share study materials from favourite friends then this one is for you and important things is that I would mention what ever errors I got, those fixes also explained</description></item><item><title>Data_nomalization</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/offtopic/data_nomalization/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:19:17 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/offtopic/data_nomalization/</guid><description>In this article what ever i give the information is based on my personal experience so i think my personal setup may help you guys thats why i recommend you to use this setup
i am taking what ever your requirement wise that you will use in your daily drive
why need to documentation #first of all why we need to document something, well small kind of things will doesnt matter but when it comes to like making a project or gathering some big data or learning something and you opened it again and you will know that you have forgotten that thing which you were fantastic at that thing few months back or few years back, you may have get this kind of problem in your life right?</description></item><item><title>Terms and Conditions</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/terms-and-conditions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:32:47 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/terms-and-conditions/</guid><description>Welcome to MahaboobTech!
These terms and conditions outline the rules and regulations for the use of MahaboobTech&amp;rsquo;s Website, located at mahaboobtech.in.
1. Introduction #By accessing this website we assume you accept these terms and conditions. Do not continue to use MahaboobTech if you do not agree to take all of the terms and conditions stated on this page.
2. Services Provided #MahaboobTech provides technology information and blogging services. The content is provided for general informational purposes only.</description></item><item><title>about</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:32:31 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/about/</guid><description>Who am I? #Briefly about me #Hi, this is Shaik Mahaboob Basha. You can call me Bs or Basha, as you like. I am a B.Tech graduate who loves to explore tech things. I just forget about myself when I work on technical things, and I love to explore mainly operating systems, coding, and designing circuits. Sometimes my interest expands to various things, but mostly I love to do technical stuff like Iron Man.</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/privacy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 14:32:31 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/privacy/</guid><description>Welcome to MahaboobTech!
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data. This privacy policy will inform you about how we look after your personal data when you visit our website mahaboobtech.in and tell you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.
1. Important Information and Who We Are #Controller
MahaboobTech is the controller and responsible for your personal data (collectively referred to as &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo; in this privacy policy).</description></item><item><title>What is linux</title><link>https://mahaboobtech.in/tech/os/what_is_linux/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 22:50:44 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mahaboobtech.in/tech/os/what_is_linux/</guid><description>What is Linux? #Linux is an operating system. To a newbie, it might seem like just an operating system, but technically, it&amp;rsquo;s a kernel. Now, what is a kernel? You might wonder. In a nutshell, it acts as a bridge between hardware and software. Yes, Linux is a kernel created by Sir Linus Torvalds.
There were a few software projects like GNU and other open-source software. When combined with the Linux kernel, they form the complete operating system.</description></item></channel></rss>