<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mahaboobtech</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/</link>
    <description>Recent content on mahaboobtech</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 07:18:08 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/offtopic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hyderabad Foods</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/hyderabad-foods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 07:18:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/hyderabad-foods/</guid>
      <description>hello bhojana priyulara 😂, i am making the blog for food lovers who are at hyderabad, in this blog i will mention few places and few dishes which are famous in Hyderabad which you need definately try it atleast once in your life.&#xA;note this blog may update time to time, if you know few famous places &amp;amp; dishes you can email us about that particular place email : mickelbasha1268@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quotes Logic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/quotes-logic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 16:28:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/quotes-logic/</guid>
      <description>life #welcome here guys, this one is special blog because it is wrote with a lot of experience and feelings. here i am going to give few quotes which i think it may impact in your life and may help to superfiy your way of living and realize the motive of the life and to know how beautifull is life, to know how painfull is life , to know how this life journey is &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relationship</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/relationship/</guid>
      <description>If you want to maintain a good, healthy relationship, then this article is for you, especially for introverts who are hesitant to talk.&#xA;Feeling of Introverts #Introverts in relationships often face difficulties maintaining connections. Especially in boyfriend-girlfriend relationships, they tend to stay silent and not talk much. However, they wish they could be like Remo in the movie Aparichith. Introverts often rely on facial expressions; they don&amp;rsquo;t talk much but instead observe others and stay silent, which leads to their behavior going unrecognized.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data_nomalization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/data_nomalization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:19:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/data_nomalization/</guid>
      <description>In this article what ever i give the information is based on my personal experience so i think my personal setup may help you guys thats why i recommend you to use this setup&#xA;i am taking what ever your requirement wise that you will use in your daily drive&#xA;why need to documentation #first of all why we need to document something, well small kind of things will doesnt matter but when it comes to like making a project or gathering some big data or learning something and you opened it again and you will know that you have forgotten that thing which you were fantastic at that thing few months back or few years back, you may have get this kind of problem in your life right?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Job scams</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/job_scams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:53:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/job_scams/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyderabad</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/hyderabad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/offtopic/hyderabad/</guid>
      <description>i love hyderabad because of charminar</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
